Guide to the Riggs Family papers, 1672-2006 MS2239
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Paper documents, circa 1785 - 2006; Series 3; 3 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence, 1832-2006; 1942-1950; Series 3 Subseries 1; 6.25 Linear Feet 12 document boxes 1 slim document box
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 April 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 May 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 June 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 July 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 July 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 July 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 August 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 September 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 September 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1950 December 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1951 January 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1951 February 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1951 March 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1954 May 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1954 June 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1955 January 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1955 January 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1955 February 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1955 June 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1956 July 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1956 July 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1956 July 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1956 July 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1961 May 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 March 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 March 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 July 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 August 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 September 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 September 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 September 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 October 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 October 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 October 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 November 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 November 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1962 December 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 January 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1963 February 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 January 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 May 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 July 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 July 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 August 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1972 September 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1973 March 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1974 August 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1975 June 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1975 June 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1975 September 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1975 November 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1975 November 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1986 December 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1988 June 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1990 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 October 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      Letter contains a memorandum of what John Beverley Riggs wanted done in case of his death.
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 June 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 June 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 July 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 November 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1944 December 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 January 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 February 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 April 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 May 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 July 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 September 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 October 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1945 December 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1949 November 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 68)
      Includes newsclippings of articles written by Henriette de Sieyes Riggs as an undercover dime-a-dance hall dancer 1949 November. She was Thomas Riggs, Jr.'s wife.
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1950 March 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1962 November 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, 1975 August 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 71)
    - Letters from John Beverley Riggs, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 72)
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [1 of 6], 1943; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Includes negatives and photos of Thomas Riggs Jr in Africa 1943 and at 1910 S St, NW, Washington, DC in 1943.
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [2 of 6], 1942-1953; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [3 of 6], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [4 of 6], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Includes photos from Africa in 1942 and notes written by Thomas Riggs Jr on the campaign in Europe 1942 June 25.
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [5 of 6], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [6 of 6], 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [1 of 3], 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [2 of 3], 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr [3 of 3], 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr army and after [1 of 5], 1943; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr army and after [2 of 5], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Includes pictures of Thomas Riggs Jr.
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr army and after [3 of 5], 1941-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr army and after [4 of 5], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - More letters home from Thomas Riggs Jr army and after [5 of 5], 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Calling cards - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Letters - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, A [1 of 5], 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Letters - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, B - D [2 of 5], 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Letters - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, E - J [3 of 5], 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Letters - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, K - R [4 of 5], 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Letters - death of Governor Thomas Riggs, S - Z [5 of 5], 1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Letters to and from Governor Thomas Riggs, Jessie Howard, and others, 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Letters regarding Maryland Historical Society, 1939-1963; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Letters regarding TR - Riggs, E. Francis Riggs, 1934; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Letters to and from John Beverley Riggs and Governor Thomas Riggs, 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Letters to and from John Beverley Riggs, Thomas Riggs Jr, and family, 1945-1951; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Letters regarding Thomas Riggs Jr, Iseley etc, 1943-2006; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Letters regarding Governor Thomas Riggs, 1935-1945; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Letters regarding RECUM, Baroness Marie, and the others, 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Letters regarding Riggs family portraits and miniatures, 1943-1949; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Letters regarding Riggs family and research, 1962-1963; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Letters to and from John Beverley Riggs and Wilmarth Lewis, 1962-1963; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs regarding Rev. Lawrason Riggs' estate, 1943-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Letters regarding miniature of John Singleton by Charles Willson Peale, 1955; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Letters regarding a guide to American history in London, 1900-1909; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Typed copies.
    - Letters regarding Renee Coudert Riggs, 1924 November 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Renee Coudert Riggs was Thomas Riggs' wife.
    - Letters to and from Franz V. Recum and Thomas Riggs, 1942-1944; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Letters regarding Riggs family and Corcoran, 1962; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Letters regarding research requests, 1960-1966; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      To and from John Beverley Riggs.
    - E. Riggs and son Lawrason Riggs letters and accounts St. Louis, 1843; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Personal business, 1785-2004; 1939-1962; Series 3 Subseries 2; 1.25 Linear Feet 2 document boxes 1 slim document box
    This subseries contains business records for John Beverley Riggs and additional Riggs family members including Thomas (Tommy) Riggs, Jr. and Renee Coudert Riggs. It consists of book order receipts, travel itineraries, legal documents, and account books. The materials date from 1785 – 2004, with the bulk of the material ranging from 1939 - 1962.
    - Order forms for John Beverley Riggs book on Riggs family [1 of 3], 1939; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Order forms for John Beverley Riggs book on Riggs family [2 of 3], 1939; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Order forms for John Beverley Riggs book on Riggs family [3 of 3], 1939; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Accounts of John Beverley Riggs - Riggs family book, 1939; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - John Beverley Riggs' furlough certificate, 1945 January 10; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Accounts of John Beverley Riggs - Brookeville, Maryland, 1946; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Baggage slip of John Beverley Riggs, undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Riggs contributions to Mt. Vernon, 1980 June 2; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Lawrason Riggs passport copies, 1859 May 20; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Estate of Renee Coudert Riggs - (Thomas Riggs) - Portraits, 1963; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      Wife of Thomas Riggs.
    - Invoices and letters for shipping c/o Lawrason Riggs, 1833; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Ventures with George Washington Riggs, Elisha Riggs, and others. Invoices for Maritime trade to Mexico, Souther America, and elsewhere.
    - John Beverley Riggs personal buisiness papers, 1939-1962; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Inventories, legal papers, letters from lawyers regarding Thomas Riggs, Jr estate, 1953-1954; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Riggs trip to Europe, 1956; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - John Beverley Riggs - National Trust Conference, 1962 October; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Old accounts book from Oak Grove, circa 1785; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Estate of Elisha Riggs - George Washington Riggs, Jr., Joseph K. Riggs executors [1 of 2], 1853; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Estate of Elisha Riggs - George Washington Riggs, Jr., Joseph K. Riggs executors [2 of 2], 1853; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Inventory of #6 Bowling Green, New York signed by Elisha Riggs, 1841-1848; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      At letters: F) House furniture G) Fire stocks R) Railroad bonds (totaling $3,550,000) W) Wines
    - Account book for shipping to Central and South America, etc, 1832; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Commerce from New York. Also business name listing.
  - Publications and research, 1939-1956; Series 3 Subseries 3; 1.5 Linear Feet 2 document boxes 2 slim document boxes
    This subseries contains genealogy research and draft manuscripts written by John Beverley Riggs and Thomas (Tommy) Riggs, Jr. The bulk of the material ranges from 1939 – 1956.